[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What nickname has been given to the U.S. state of Rhode Island?", "correct_answer": "Ocean State", "incorrect_answers": ["Marine State", "Island State", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the phrase to be blue (blau sein) mean in German language?", "correct_answer": "To be drunk", "incorrect_answers": ["To cheat on your wife", "To be pregnant", "To be angry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why does a cat rub against your leg?", "correct_answer": "To mark you by depositing his/ her scent", "incorrect_answers": ["Because she/ he really likes you.", "Because it feels good.", "To show he/ she trusts you"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this 1992 thriller, Bridget Fonda plays a woman who seeks a roommate through an ad.", "correct_answer": "Single White Female", "incorrect_answers": ["Crazy Is Never Enough", "Roomies", "The Ad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Epic Movie, Edward and Jack Swallows first meet in the beavers house.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chihuahuas are prone to hypoglycemia (low blood sugar).", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the metric prefix nano mean?", "correct_answer": "1/1,000,000,000", "incorrect_answers": ["1,000,000", "1,000,000,000", "10"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of professionals does the 1970 comedy movie MASH describe?", "correct_answer": "Doctors", "incorrect_answers": ["Dancers", "Cooks", "Baseball players"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to U.S. intelligence, the Red October, a Soviet ballistic missile submarine, featured in the movie The Hunt for Red October, is a member of what submarine classification?", "correct_answer": "Typhoon Class", "incorrect_answers": ["Los Angeles Class", "Cyclone Class", "Dallas Class"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the nickname of the leader of the kidnappers in the 2004 action thriller movie Man on Fire?", "correct_answer": "The Voice", "incorrect_answers": ["El Padre", "El Caliente", "The Fingers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first full length animated movie was made and released in this country.", "correct_answer": "Argentina", "incorrect_answers": ["Italy", "China", "Germany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jean Shepherd narrated A Christmas Story and its sequel My Summer Story.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]